http://www.alfordbishop.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Contact Us
Shortlist (0)
Call Us On 01892 518766
Shortlist (0)
Alford & Bishop Privacy Policy
Alford & Bishop Legal Recruitment is specialist legal recruitment company who are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
About this Policy
This policy sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be treated. The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) is a new regulation which replaces the Data Protection Regulation (Directive 95/46/EC). The Regulation aims to work as one with data protection legislation across EU member states, enhancing privacy rights for individuals and providing a strict framework within which commercial organisations can legally operate.
Even though the UK has bought to light its intention to leave the EU in 2019, the GDPR will be applicable in the UK from 25th May 2018. The Government intends for the GDPR to continue in UK law post Brexit and has also introduced a Data Protection Bill to replace the current Data Protection Act. Your new rights under the GDPR are set out in this policy but will only apply once the GDPR becomes law on 25th May 2018. Where you provide us with your personal information in person, by email, through our websites, job boards, social media or via any other method you consent to the collection and use of this information by Alford & Bishop in accordance with this privacy policy.
Who We Are & What We Do
We are legal recruitment specialists offering a personal service to candidates and clients alike. We recruit lawyers for private practice, commerce and industry across Southern England. Many of our clients and candidates come to us via recommendation and referral. Our service is fully confidential to both candidates and clients. We do not submit CV's without the candidate's consent.
We collect the personal data of the following types of people to allow us to undertake our business.
Prospective and placed candidates for permanent roles
Potential and current clients
Prospective and live client contacts
Employees and Employers
When you visit and navigate our site and when you communicate with us via our site, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. We collect information about you to carry out our core business and ancillary activities.
How can you correct or delete your personal data form the Alford & Bishop website?
If you believe that the personal data we have about you is incorrect, you are welcome to contact us so that we can update it and keep your data accurate and up to date. If at any point you wish for us to update or delete information from the Alford & Bishop database, you can simply call or email us. Please ensure that any CV provided to us is updated from time to time in accordance with your current circumstances.
Cookies and Tags
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users and to provide you with a unique and tailored experience when you browse our website. This also allows us to improve our Website.
By using our website you are agreeing to the use of cookies as described.
Security
We have adopted and adhere to stringent security standards designed to protect non-public personal information against accidental or unauthorized access or disclosure.
We have a number of safeguards for our sites and systems, physical and technical barriers that together form a protective firewall around the information stored.
Updates to This Statement
We may change this Statement from time to time; when updates are made.  We encourage you to periodically reread this Policy to see if there have been any changes that may affect you. This Statement is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
Browse Jobs
Family & ChildcareEmploymentResidential Property & ConveyancingPI & Clinical NegligenceCommercial PropertyProperty LitigationPrivate ClientCommercial LitigationCivil LitigationImmigrationInsolvency & Debt RecoveryInsurance LitigationLegal CashierIP & ITHousingConstructionCrimeCorporateCompany CommercialPractice Manager
Contact Us
Alford & BishopThe BreweryBells Yew GreenTunbridge WellsKentTN3 9BDUnited Kingdom
